{
    "subject": "resource/Jo_Van_Fleet",
    "predicate": "property/deathPlace",
    "object": "Jamaica, New York, U.S.",
    "human_readable": "Jo Van Fleet died in Jamaica, New York, U.S.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.851203441619873,
            "question": "Where did Jo Van Fleet die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709487080574036,
            "question": "When did Jo Van Fleet die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7099299430847168,
            "question": "Was Jo Van Fleet's place of death in a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6455026865005493,
            "question": "What country was Jo Van Fleet's place of death in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44632139801979065,
            "question": "What was Jo Van Fleet known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44564318656921387,
            "question": "In what state did Jo Van Fleet pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.421122670173645,
            "question": "Was Jo Van Fleet an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29412874579429626,
            "question": "Where is Jamaica, New York located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22403889894485474,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Jo Van Fleet's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2043823003768921,
            "question": "Did Jo Van Fleet win any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jo Van Fleet died in Jamaica, New York, U.S.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2475_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Jo Van Fleet's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2475_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Jamaica, New York located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2475_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Jo Van Fleet an actress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2475_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2475_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Jo Van Fleet died on June 10, 1996, at Jamaica Hospital in Jamaica, Queens, New York City, New York, U.S., which supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}